sendhub.com 2014-07-03

# Privacy Policy - SendHub

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

We may amend this policy at any time. All amended terms automatically take effect 10 days after they are initially posted on the Website. You agree that notice on the Website of changes to the policy is sufficient notice. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this policy will mean that you accept those changes.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy our Terms of Use, we retain the right to review your account in order to determine whether or not there has been a violation of our Terms of Use. In such case that we determine there has been a violation of our Terms of Use, we retain the right to suspend or delete your account without prior notice.

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.

We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain your consent or as required by law.

We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

We will collect personal information by lawful means and, where appropriate, with your knowledge or consent.

We do not track or honor “Do Not Track” signals sent from any web browser or any other device, mechanism, or software used to access the Website.

Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

It is your responsibility to protect your personal data and maintain the confidentiality of your user information and password. You are also responsible for immediately notifying InfoReach of any unauthorized use of your account, or breach of your account information or password. InfoReach will not be liable for any loss that You may incur as a result of someone else using Your username or password, either with or without Your knowledge. You shall be liable for any expenses, including usage charges and fines, fees, civil judgments, and reasonable attorney’s fees for your failure to promptly notify of unauthorized use of your account or breach of your account information or password.

An Internet Protocol address is a number that automatically identifies the computer/machine you have used to access the Internet. The address enables our server to send you the webpages that you want to visit, and it may disclose the server owned by your Internet Service Provider. We utilize your Internet Protocol address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our site.

Like many other websites, the Site employs cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to a user's computer for purposes of storing information about a user's preferences. Cookies do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. A user can set his or her browser to refuse cookies, however, he or she may not be able to take full advantage of the site.

Our web pages use web beacons in conjunction with cookies to compile aggregate statistics about website usage. A web beacon is an electronic image called an action tag, or single-pixel (1 x 1), or clear GIF. Web beacons serve many of the same purposes as cookies. In addition, web beacons are used to track the traffic patterns of users from one page to another in order to maximize web traffic flow. Some web beacons may be unusable if you elect to reject their associated cookies.

We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. InfoReach understands the importance of protecting children's privacy online. The Website is not intended for children 13 years of age or younger. It is not our policy to intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

We do not rent, sell, or otherwise provide your personal information to third parties. We do, however, reserve the right to share personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with trusted partners. This data shared to and analyzed by our trusted partners is used for the betterment of our products, services, and the overall experience of our customers. Such sharing occurs for purposes of developing website analytics, improvement of engagement, prevention of SPAM, and as an aid to diagnose and repair bugs. We may also use personal information to provide you updates on the status of the Website, your account, or the service.

If you post Personal Information about your contacts, we will not communicate with those contacts without your consent, nor will we provide this information to third parties, unless compelled by law, necessary to enforce our User Agreement or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of InfoReach, its users, the Site, or the public.

It is possible that we may need to disclose Personal Information, profile information and/or information about your activities as an InfoReach user when required by subpoena or other legal process, or if InfoReach has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary:

  1. to investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies;
  2. to enforce the TOU, to investigate and defend InfoReach against any third-party claims or allegations, or to protect the security or integrity of our Site; and/or
  3. to exercise or protect the rights, property or personal safety of InfoReach, our users, employees or others.

Although we do not currently include advertisements in our Site, we may do so in the future. Any such advertisements would be hosted within other Site features, and we would not provide your email address to advertisers.

InfoReach may also need to share Personal Information if our ownership status changes. For example, we may need to share Personal Information with a company that acquires us.

Despite any precautions we take, the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, and we therefore cannot ensure or warrant the security of information you transmit to InfoReach. You acknowledge that you provide such information at your own risk. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Emails, instant messages, and similar means of communication with other users are not encrypted, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means. Although we attempt to block the upload of certain file types known to pose a security risk, we recommend that you scan user-uploaded attachments with a virus checker before opening them.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. If you have any questions about the policy, please contact: [support@sendhub.com](mailto:support@sendhub.com).
